indiabullsdhani.com 2019-04-24

# Privacy Policy of Personal Loans | Indiabulls Dhani

At Indiabulls Consumer Finance Limited(formerly IVL Finance Limited and Shivshakti Financial Services Limited), a company incorporated under the provisions of Companies Act, 1956, having our registered office at M-62&63, First Floor, Connaught Place, New Delhi – 110 001 and having corporate identity number U74899DL1994PLC062407, hereinafter referred to as “IBCFL”, we value your trust and respect your privacy.

This Privacy Policy provides you with details about the manner in which your data is collected, stored and used by us. You are advised to read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting IBCFL’s website/IBCFL mobile applications, you expressly give us consent to use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use or access IBCFL website or IBCFL mobile applications.

I General

This privacy statement is applicable to website of IBCFL, or any online/mobile application that refers to or links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, our “Services”). This Privacy Policy applies regardless of whether you use a computer, mobile phone, tablet, or television or any other media or computer resource to access our Services. It is important that you read the Privacy Policy carefully because anytime you use our Services, you consent to the practices/ policies that we have set out in this Privacy Policy.

II Personal Information

Personal Information, means and includes, all information that can be linked to a specific individual or to identity of any individual, including but not limited to, name, address, mailing address, telephone number, email ID, bank account details including details linked to credit/debit payment instruments, information about your mobile phone, any details that may have been voluntarily provided by the customer, whether to Unique Identification Authority of India (UIDAI), Credit Information Bureau of India Limited (CIBIL) or any other agency including any other Credit Information Companies.

Information obtained with consent from your mobile device like device location, device information (including storage, model, installed apps, wifi, mobile network) transactional and promotional SMS, communication information including contacts and call logs

III Use of Personal Information

We use personal information to provide you with personal loan you explicitly requested for, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot concerns, help promote safe services, assess your interest in our services, inform you about offers, products, services, updates, customize your experience, detect and protect us against errors, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our terms and conditions, etc. We may also use your personal information to send you offers regarding various services/facilities which IBCFL or its group companies may, from time to time, launch. We may occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, gender, etc.). We use this data to customize your experience at IBCFL.

IV Disclosure

We will not voluntarily disclose your personal information to any third party but in exceptional circumstances, we may do so if we are required by a court order, by Government Authorities, by law enforcement authorities or by other legal processes or where it becomes necessary to do so to protect the rights or property of IBCFL and/or its group companies/affiliates, etc. We may also disclose your information to a third party as part of a merger or transfer or any restructuring.

V Cookies

A “cookie” is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. IBCFL uses cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered.No personal information/ data/details will be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

VI Password policy

Do help us protect your privacy by maintaining the secrecy of the username and password you use for any of our Services.

VII Changes to this Privacy Policy

IBCFL reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy or any other of our policies/practices at any time without giving any prior notification; hence, you are requested to review the Privacy Policy periodically, to make sure that you are aware of any such changes. This Privacy Policy shall apply uniformly to IBCFL website and IBCFL mobile applications or any other media used by IBCFL for its Services. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting the same on our web site at www.indiabullsdhani.com

VIII Consent To International Transfer Of Data

By using or participating in any Service and/or providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage and processing of your information outside India, consistent with this Privacy Policy. Please note that the data protection laws of countries to which your information may be transferred shall be at same level as that of India.

IX Data Retention

We take reasonable steps to ensure that information about you is available only for so long as is necessary for the purpose for which it is processed, or longer if required under any contract, by applicable law, or for statistical purposes, subject to appropriate safeguards.

X Third-Party Links And Content On Our Services

Our Services may link to third-party websites and services that are outside our control. Further, IBCFL, its group companies, its affiliates, and their directors and employees (“IBCFL Group”) accept no liability and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising directly or indirectly (including special, incidental or consequential, punitive, or exemplary loss, damage or expenses) from your use of any mobile application or any site or inability to use by any party, howsoever arising, and including any loss, damage or expense arising from, but not limited to, any defect, error, omission, interruption, imperfection, fault, mistake or inaccuracy with any mobile or online application, its Contents (material, information, data, money market movements, news items, etc.) or associated services, or due to unavailability of any application or any part thereof or any Contents or associated services even if IBCFL Group are advised of the possibility of such damages, losses or expenses.

XI Intellectual Property Rights

Please note that IBCFL retains all rights (including copyrights, trademarks, patents as well as any other intellectual property right) in relation to all information provided on or via this web site (including all texts, graphics and logos).

XII Consent

You consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose to IBCFL in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to your consent for sharing your information as per this Privacy Policy.

XIII Disclaimer

Kindly note that IBCFL does not collect personal information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. Upon such voluntary disclosure of personal information, we may further verify, collate or receive information about you from publicly and commercially available sources (as permitted by law), which we may combine with other information we receive from you. We may also receive information about you from third-party social networking services if you are already connected with those services. IBCFL shall, at all times, ensure to implement reasonable security practices and procedures (such as managerial, operational, physical and technical) for the purpose of protection and safeguarding of your personal data and information as the same is of vital importance to IBCFL . At IBCFL, we are strongly committed to protecting the personal and financial information that you submit to us. Personal information of individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your approval at the time of collection. However, please note that although we take reasonable steps to protect your information, no website, internet transmission, computer system or wireless connection is completely secure.

IBCFL shall ensure to safeguard the security and confidentiality of any information you share with us. Any of your personally identifiable information obtained by us shall not be used or shared other than for the purposes to which you consent. However, despite our utmost efforts to protect your personal information, IBCFL cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us through our online services/ applications. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you accept that such transmission of your personal information is done at your own risk.

Your information/inputs/queries as a registered user are required to serve you better and the same shall not be shared with anyone without your consent. However, we may disclose your personal data to agents or contractors of IBCFL and/or its group companies/affiliates to enable processing of transactions or communications with you “on need” basis. Your aforesaid information may be further used for assessment and analysis of our market, customers, products, and services and to understand the way people use our Services so that we can improve them and develop new products and services. However, it shall be on the basis that the agents are required to keep the information confidential and will not use the information for any other purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for IBCFL and/or its group companies/affiliates.

XIV No contractual obligation

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party, nor is it intended to do so.
